JULY 9TH
'7월 9일'
LIFE THEATER
'인생극장'
I blew it again.
또 날렸다
That was my 17,711th attempt!
그건 17,711번째 시도였어
Won't leave
떠나려면
Without a dropkick on her
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas
자자스 자자스 나사타나다 자자스
-She summoned me, the evil god -Evil god
- 저 애가 소환한 난 악마다 - 악마다!
-I gotta kill her or else -What?
저 애를 죽이지 않으면 뭐?
-I can't go back to hell -Sister...
지옥에 갈 수가 없어 자매여...
Yeah, yeah, yeah Life next to death, I combat with my chainsaw
그래! 그래! 그래! 죽음과 살기 위해, 전기톱으로 싸워야지!
If you go too far
네가 막 나가면
I'll slice you up completely
널 완전히 썰어버릴 거야!
Your halo Must get it back
네 후광을 반드시 되찾아야지!
-Never miss a chance -Hey, seriously?
기회를 절대 놓치지 마 정말 그럴 거야?
-To attack her from behind -You're so mean
뒤에서 공격하려고? 넌 못됐어
I'll never give up
난 절대 포기 안 해
Yurine, you're off your guard!
유리네, 방심하고 있군!
Now! Time to finish you with the Royal Copenhagen!
지금이다! 로열코펜하겐으로 끝내주지!
Huh? What? I missed...
어, 뭐지? 실패다...
Can't leave Earth
지구를 떠나려면
Without a dropkick on her
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
But until then
하지만 그때까진
-Let's all have fun together -Yeah!
모두 같이 놀자! 신난다!
Medusa!
메두사!
What is it, Jashin-chan? You look so serious.
사신짱, 무슨 일이야? 표정이 아주 심각해
-We're going to the bank. -What?
- 은행으로 간다 - 뭐?
No, resist that urge! Don't rob the bank!
안 돼, 충동을 참아! 은행은 털지 마!
Please don't!
제발 그러지 마!
Chill out. We're just withdrawing your money.
진정해 네 돈만 찾는 거야
Oh, you got me there.
아, 그거였구나?
Well, the slots got me.
슬롯머신이 날 이겼어
-I'm so relieved. -Don't be.
- 안심이다 - 안심하지 마라
My actions rewrite history.
내 행동은 역사를 다시 쓴다
This is the last time.
이게 마지막이야
Now, let's get going to the bank.
자, 은행에 가자
How the hell did we end up in the middle of a bank robbery?
어쩌다 은행 강도 사건에 휘말리게 된 거냐고?
Don't make a sound!
소리 내지 마!
Don't get smart with us.
허튼짓할 생각도 마라
I should have sent you here alone.
널 혼자 보내는 건데
I never signed up for this!
난 이런 거 원한 적 없어!
You! Viper girl, cut the whining or I'll kill you.
너, 독사녀 징징거리면 죽여버린다
I don't care what happens to her, just spare my life, won't you?
얘한테 뭘 해도 상관없으니 내 목숨은 살려줘요
How could you!
너 어떻게 이래?
Another word and you're both dead.
한마디만 더 하면 너흰 둘 다 죽는다
Mom, I wanna play cards.
엄마, 카드 게임 할래
-Quiet, not now. -This sucks.
- 조용히 해, 지금은 안 돼 - 짜증 나
Jashin-chan, do you think your dropkick could take these humans out?
사신짱, 네 드롭킥으로 이 사람들을 처치할 수 있니?
You're a devil, you should punish them.
넌 악마니까 저 사람들 벌줘야 해
But if I miss, they'd kill me. Why risk my life?
실수하면 날 죽일 텐데 왜 내 목숨을 걸어?
Even devils aren't immune to a bullet in the head.
악마라도 총알이 머리에 박히면 어쩔 수 없어
But you have to protect everyone!
하지만 사람들을 보호해야 해
Mom, I'm starving.
엄마, 배고파
Hang in there.
조금만 참아
I'm supposed to take my meds right now.
지금 약 먹을 시간인데
I can't let my pet chick starve to death.
내 애완 병아리를 굶겨 죽일 수 없어요
I can't afford to miss today's business meeting.
오늘 꼭 참석해야 할 회사 미팅이 있어
I'm missing out on Miyutan's handshake event.
미유탄 악수 행사를 못 가게 됐다
Guess I'm late for work.
직장에 지각하겠어
-Baby coming... -I'm going to pee my pants!
- 아기가 나오는데... - 바지에 소변을 싸겠어!
Fine, all right.
좋아, 그럼
Jashin-chan!
사신짱!
If you're so inclined, go for it.
네가 그렇게 하고 싶다면 해보라고
I'll be an innocent bystander who lives.
난 결백한 구경꾼으로 살아남을 거야
I should look for another gig.
다른 아르바이트를 찾아야겠군
-Baby... -I need those meds to stay thin.
- 아기가... - 날씬하려면 그 약을 먹어야 해
-This is horrible! -My poor chick!
- 이건 끔찍해! - 내 불쌍한 병아리!
You're really going for it?
너 정말 할 거야?
Yes.
응
-Are we done? -No, not yet.
- 다 됐어? - 아니, 아직이야
Hey, move again and you're dead.
야, 또 움직이면 죽는다
What's with the paper bag?
이 종이 봉지는 뭐야?
Excuse me, would you please take a look at my eyes?
실례합니다, 두 분 제 눈을 봐 주실래요?
Hey, she's pretty cute!
야, 정말 예쁘다
Well done.
잘했어
Everyone, we're safe now.
여러분, 이제 모두 안전합니다
-What just happened? -No idea, but we're safe now!
- 방금 무슨 일이 있었죠? - 몰라, 하지만 이제 우린 안전해
She looks like Miyutan!
저 여자는 미유탄을 닮았다
-Thank you. -Paper bag girl!
- 고마워요 - 종이 봉지 소녀!
Thanks.
고맙습니다
The baby's born, I'm ecstatic.
아기가 태어났어요 정말 황홀해요
I couldn't hold it. It's all lukewarm for me.
난 참지 못했어요 온몸이 미지근해요
My dropkick would've been just as effective, you know.
내 드롭킥도 이 정도 효과가 있었을 텐데
But I'll let Medusa take all the credit here.
메두사의 공을 인정해야지
Orochimaru! That was quite a feat!
오로치마루! 정말 대단한 일을 했어
Oh, that was nothing, really.
아니, 그 정도쯤이야 아무것도 아니지
Couldn't do it without my partner, Medusa.
내 파트너인 메두사가 없었으면 할 수 없는 일이지
Hey, paper bag girl.
어이, 종이 봉지 소녀
When will they de-fossilize?
저 사람들은 언제 화석에서 풀려나는 거야?
Oh, eventually.
언젠가는요
-Gotcha! Leave the rest to us! -Thank you.
- 알겠어! 나머지는 우리에게 맡겨 - 고마워요
Let's go, Orochimaru.
가자, 오로치마루
-Where? -Oh, come on.
- 어디? - 알잖아
I'm gonna make you mine today.
오늘은 널 내 거로 만들 거야
-You're under arrest! -No way in hell!
- 널 체포한다! - 절대 안 돼!
-Medusa, help! -Not my problem.
- 메두사, 도와줘! - 내 문제가 아니야
Bank robber arrest victory! Now that's Insta-worthy.
은행 강도 체포 승리! 인스타에 올릴 만한 일이지
Hashtag "no money stolen."
#'훔친 돈 없음'
Hashtag "but my heart was."
#'하지만 내 마음을 훔침'
Hashtag "I love Orochimaru."
#'내 사랑 오로치마루'
I need you! ATM!
ATM! 네가 필요해!
You're on your own, deceiver.
네가 알아서 해, 사기꾼아
The ATMs are over there.
ATM은 저기 있다
What? You traitor!
뭐? 이 배신자!
I should've known!
알았어야 했어!
The number of bank robberies in Japan peaked in 2001.
일본에서 발생한 은행 강도 건수는 2001년에 가장 많았습니다
Since then, they have decreased.
그 이후로 감소했죠
Instead, low-risk crimes like bank transfer scams have sky-rocketed.
대신 계좌이체 사기 같은 낮은 위험의 범죄율이 치솟고 있습니다
Don't be a victim. Check-in with your parents frequently.
피해 보지 않도록 부모님과 자주 연락해 확인하세요
But history's changed now!
하지만 역사는 이제 바뀌었다
My bag ripped.
내 봉지가 찢어졌네
Use this.
이걸 써
Thanks, that's good for now.
고마워, 당분간은 그걸로 되겠다
But nothing tops craft paper bags when it comes to comfort, texture and smell.
하지만 크래프트 종이 봉지가 제일 좋아 편하고 감촉과 냄새도 좋거든
Never knew you were so particular.
그렇게 까다로운지 몰랐네
It's a new day!
새로운 날이다!
Time to deliver the milk!
우유 배달할 시간이군
MILK
'우유'
There! That's it for today.
됐어! 오늘 배달은 끝났다
Sweet. I was a second faster than last time!
좋아, 지난번보다 1초 빨랐어
At this rate, I'll eventually make a zero-second record!
이 상태라면 내가 결국 0초 기록을 세울 거야!
Oh, I wish!
정말 그러고 싶어
Seconds, please!
한 공기 더 부탁해
-You've got quite the appetite. -She's got no shame.
- 식욕이 넘치는구나 - 창피하지도 않니?
You're just a great cook, Jashin-chan.
넌 정말 대단한 요리사야, 사신짱
I know. No need to say it.
아니까 말할 필요 없어
Here you go.
받아
Just like the folktales.
꼭 옛날이야기와 같아
Like this one.
이것처럼요
Where does that energy come from?
그 힘이 어디서 생기는 거야?
Never caught a cold as a child either.
어렸을 때도 감기 한 번 안 걸렸어
They do say that fools never catch colds.
사람들이 바보는 감기에 안 걸린대
I've never caught a cold either.
나도 감기에 걸린 적 없지
Because I'm a fool.
난 바보니까
Are you okay on time?
시간은 괜찮니?
Shoot, I'm gonna be late.
이런, 지각하겠다
Thanks for breakfast! See you!
아침 고마워, 갈게!
Minos works so hard.
미노스는 너무 열심히 일해
The complete opposite of someone I know.
내가 아는 누구와 정반대지
I'm a devoted homemaker.
난 헌신적인 가정주부야
Here we go.
가자
We're glad to have you here.
네가 여기서 일해줘서 고맙다
You can count on me.
제게 맡기세요
-It's so heavy... -Hey, little one!
- 너무 무거워... - 어이, 꼬맹이!
Me?
저요?
Yeah, you! Little one! I'm talking to you.
그래, 너, 꼬맹이 너한테 말하는 거다
You're moving too slow. Wake up, will you?
넌 동작이 너무 느려 정신 차려
Why do I have to be treated like a slave in order to survive?
왜 난 살아남으려면 노예 취급을 받아야 하지?
Leave the heavy-lifting to me.
무거운 거 드는 일은 나한테 맡겨
Go get assigned another task.
너는 다른 일을 달라고 해
Thank you so much.
정말 고마워
No biggie.
별거 아니야
She's so bright.
저 애는 너무 밝아
She is a devil, right?
쟤가 악마가 맞나?
Another busy day of work all done!
또 바쁜 하루가 끝났다
Time to jog back home.
집까지 달려야지
Thanks for--
고마워...
I couldn't even thank her. I'm such a loser.
난 쟤에게 감사도 할 수 없어 난 정말 못났다
I will next time.
다음엔 해야지
Will I ever get to see Jashin-chan?
사신짱을 만날 수 있을까?
-My bad! Are you okay? -Yes.
- 내 실수야, 괜찮니? - 네
Good, I'm glad.
좋아, 다행이다
Get home safe.
집에 조심해서 가
See you!
안녕!
She's a devil!
저 여자는 악마다!
Wait, do you know Jashin-chan? Hey!
잠깐만, 사신짱 알아요? 이봐요!
Hey, Minos!
어이, 미노스 누나!
-Let's play cards! -Play with us.
- 카드 게임 해요! - 우리랑 같이 놀아요
Sorry, kiddos, I don't have my cards with me.
미안해, 얘들아 지금은 카드가 없어
Really?
정말요?
That's a bummer.
실망이다
-Next time, I promise! -Okay, see you!
- 다음에 해, 약속할게! - 좋아요, 안녕
-Bye! -See you later!
- 안녕! - 나중에 봐요!
Hey, kiddos...
어이, 꼬마들...
I've got cards we could play with, what do you say?
난 카드가 있는데 같이 놀까? 어때?
No, we're good.
아니요, 괜찮아요
-Let's go, guys. -Yeah.
- 얘들아, 가자 - 응
-We wanted Minos. -She's got big boobs.
- 미노스 누나랑 놀고 싶은데 - 가슴이 엄청나게 크지
-Minos is really good, too. -She's got big boobs, too.
- 미노스 누나는 정말 착해 - 가슴도 아주 크고
What a day today!
대단한 하루였어
Taking a bath after a hard day's work is the best feeling ever.
힘든 일을 한 후 목욕을 하면 기분이 최고지
Yeah!
좋다!
Delicious!
맛있다
I'm ready to do it all again tomorrow!
내일 또 일할 준비가 됐다
We're both devils, but why is Minos more popular with humans? Damn it!
우린 둘 다 악마인데 왜 인간은 미노스를 더 좋아하지? 제길
You're better off extinct, humans!
너희는 멸종되는 게 나아 이 인간들아!
With that attitude, it's no surprise.
심보가 그러니 놀랄 일도 아니지
Jashin-chan Dropkick!
사신짱 드롭킥!
What do you wanna drink?
넌 뭘 마실래?
-Orange or grapefruit? -Orange.
- 오렌지? 자몽? - 오렌지
All right.
좋아
-Here you go. -That was kind of gross.
- 여기 있어 - 약간 역겹다
Jashin-chan.
사신짱
How does ramen for lunch sound?
점심으로 라면은 어때?
I'm in the mood for rice.
난 밥을 먹고 싶어
You look like you're lusting for ramen.
라면을 매우 먹고 싶어 하는 표정인데?
But I just said--
하지만 방금 말했잖아...
You want ramen, right?
라면을 먹고 싶은 거지?
Yes, I'd love to eat ramen.
네, 라면 먹고 싶어요
Here we go again.
또 이러는군
Welcome!
어서 오세요!
-Hey you! -Damn it.
- 야, 너! - 젠장
-You know her? -She almost killed me!
- 저 여자를 알아? - 얘가 날 거의 죽일 뻔했어
-I'll finish you today! -Please stop, I don't know you!
- 오늘 너를 없애주지! - 그만해요, 난 당신을 몰라요
-You can't fool me! -Stop!
- 누굴 속이려고 - 멈춰!
-Don't hurt Noel! -Step away!
- 노엘을 다치게 하지 마! - 물러서!
What? Noel? That's not your name.
뭐? 노엘? 네 이름이 아니잖아
Noel is a future idol who works here to support herself!
노엘은 여기서 돈을 버는 미래의 아이돌이야!
A sweet girl like her would never kill!
이렇게 착한 여자는 절대 누굴 죽이지 않아
An idol?
아이돌?
They look alike, but I guess she's not Poporon.
똑같이 생겼는데 포포롱이 아닌가 보군
Die!
죽어!
You're Noel?
네가 노엘이야?
Jeez, what a drag.
진짜 짜증 나네
Yes, I'm Noel Amatsuka.
네, 저는 아마츠카 노엘이에요
Pleasure to meet you!
만나서 반가워요!
Believe it or not, the ramen and fried rice killer combo originated in Jinbocho.
믿거나 말거나지만, 라면과 볶음밥의 환상적인 조합은 진보초에서 시작됐죠
What would you like today?
오늘은 뭘 드시겠어요?
Enough with the nonsense. Hurry up and order.
정신 나간 짓 다 했으면 빨리 주문해
That was close.
들킬 뻔했다
Coming right up!
바로 나옵니다
I see you hired new staff since the last time I was here.
지난번 왔을 때 없던 새 직원을 뽑으셨네요?
Yup, Noel has spiked the traffic here.
응, 노엘 덕에 식당이 북적거리지
-We come here every day. -Yup!
- 우리는 매일 와요 - 맞아요
Thanks for your support!
지지해 주셔서 고맙습니다
Today, I'll treat you to stir-fry sprouts and take it out of my pay.
오늘은 제가 숙주 볶음을 대접할게요 제 보수에서 뺄 거예요
She's treating us pigs, using her precious salary!
자신의 귀한 돈으로 우리 같은 돼지를 대접한다
Thank you so much. I'm so happy!
정말 고맙습니다, 너무 행복해요
Losers.
멍청이들
Human men get way too excited over nothing.
별거 아닌 일에 인간 남자는 너무 흥분하는군
That weird pouch. That has to be Poporon's.
저 이상한 가방은 분명히 포포롱 거다
Let's test her.
시험해 볼까?
Poporon, could I have a refill please?
포포롱, 리필 부탁해
Right away!
물론이죠!
Damn it!
젠장!
So you are Poporon!
넌 포포롱이야!
-Stop it! Viper bitch! -Don't touch our Noel!
- 하지 마! 독사 계집! - 노엘을 건드리지 마
Jashin-chan, this is a place for all of us to sit down and eat.
사신짱, 여긴 모든 사람이 앉아서 음식을 먹는 곳이다
There's no exception, Jashin-chan.
예외는 없어, 사신짱
But she--
하지만 이 애는...
Don't point.
손가락질하지 마
Mito Komon is said to be the first to have ramen in Japan.
일본에서 처음 라면을 먹은 사람이 미토 고몬이라고 합니다
But another theory suggests it was a monk during the Muromachi Period.
한편 무로마치 시대 어떤 승려라는 말도 있습니다
What you believe is up to you.
뭘 믿든 당신이 정하는 거죠
Check please.
계산할게요
Okay.
네
That was very good.
아주 맛있었어요
-I'm sorry for all the ruckus. -Yeah...
- 소란피워서 죄송해요 - 어...
We're leaving, Jashin-chan.
가자, 사신짱
As Jashin-chan said, you aren't just a human.
사신짱이 말했듯이 넌 인간이 아니야
You exert the same aura as another girl I know.
내가 아는 다른 여자애와 같은 아우라가 있다
That girl subdued the devil. She knows who I am, too.
저 애는 악마를 복종시키고 내가 누군지도 알아
Who the hell is she?
대체 누구지?
Dropkick on My Devil!
사신짱 드롭킥!
Stationery.
문방구
Since it has "station" in it, it must be a military-related defensive weapon.
'방'이란 글자가 있으니 군대와 관련된 방어 무기일 거야
Hey, Yurine.
유리네
I wanna test my defense powers, so attack me.
내 방어력을 시험하고 싶으니까 날 공격해 봐
Sure thing.
물론이지
Now, come at me!
자, 내게 덤벼!
Completely useless.
전혀 쓸모없군
You're such an idiot.
넌 정말 바보야
I can't suppress this craving for pudding.
푸딩에 대한 갈망을 참을 수 없다
There you are.
여기 있군
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
빨리, 빨리, 빨리!
After my first bite of pudding in the human world,
인간 세계에서 처음 푸딩을 한 입 맛본 후
I was instantly addicted.
금단 증세로 고통받을 만큼
To the point where I suffer withdrawal symptoms.
난 즉시 푸딩에 중독됐다
So good! It's too good!
너무 맛있어, 정말 좋다!
It permeates through my brain!
내 뇌로 스며든다
There are no other sweets that have this effect on me!
내게 이런 효과를 주는 단것은 이것밖에 없어
YURINE
'유리네'
Damn it!
큰일이다
This was Yurine's pudding!
이건 유리네 푸딩이었어
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
안 돼! 안 된다고!
I need to buy another one before she gets back!
그 애가 돌아오기 전에 하나 사 와야 해
I'm home.
나 왔어
What's wrong? Is it the end of the world?
왜 그러지? 세상이 끝나기라도 했어?
It is for me. Everything was clear before it all fell apart.
나한테는 그래, 전부 분명했는데 모든 게 무너졌어
Hey, you ate my pudding.
내 푸딩 먹었네
The invisible one.
투명이야
Watch out! There's an invisible one lurking around!
조심해! 투명이가 숨어있다
There's the culprit!
저기 범인이 있다!
I'm gonna get you! It just punched me!
내가 널 잡을 거다 이게 방금 날 쳤어
Damn you, invisible one!
못된 것, 이 투명이야!
Take this! Royal Copenha--
이걸 받아! 로열코펜하...
I won't let you get away with this!
넌 절대 도망 못 가
Damn it, it escaped.
젠장, 도망갔다
I wonder how it escaped when the window is closed.
창문이 닫혀 있는데 그게 어떻게 도망갔을까?
Oh, well...
그게...
That's because...
왜냐하면...
It went through it?
통과한 건가?
How do you see it when it's invisible?
안 보이는 걸 넌 어떻게 본 거야?
Because... it's from hell?
그건... 지옥에서 왔으니까?
I see.
그렇군
-You have pudding on your lips. -What?
- 네 입에 푸딩이 묻었어 - 뭐?
Coming.
나가요
Delivery!
택배요!
It must be from brawling with the invisible one just now.
방금 투명이와 싸움하다 묻은 걸 거야
-My order's here. -Your order?
- 내가 주문한 게 왔다 - 주문?
What did you order?
뭘 주문했어?
An iron maiden.
아이언 메이든
If you were honest about it, you could've just bought another one.
넌 정직하게 그냥 하나 더 살 수도 있었어
But you chose to mock me with a lame game of charades.
하지만 한심한 몸짓을 하며 날 조롱하기로 했지
Get me out of here!
여기서 날 내보내 줘!
You better come out before you run out of blood.
피가 다 떨어지기 전에 나오는 게 좋을 거다
I don't really have a choice, do I?
내겐 선택권이 없잖아!
No!
안 돼!
Dropkick on her, yeah her I'll take you down again
드롭킥을 날린다! 저 애야! 널 다시 무찌를 거다!
Hate you Love doesn't exist in this world
네가 싫어! 이 세상에 사랑이란 없어
Fear the dropkick An angel looks for her halo
드롭킥을 겁내라! 천사는 후광을 찾는다
As she starves to death
굶어 죽어가면서 말이야
It's a love and hate relationship
이건 애증 관계야
Can't leave each other alone
서로를 가만히 두지 않지
Like a galaxy-bursting shooting star
은하에서 터지는 유성처럼
Slowly, slowly, sneak up and die
천천히, 살금살금 몰래 다가가서 죽인다!
Test my heart, don't stop
내 마음을 떠봐 멈추지 말고
Let's go, dream on No matter human, angel or devil
가자! 꿈꿔! 인간이건 천사건 악마건
We're a happy family
우리는 행복한 가족이다 랄랄라
Let me say, I love you
내가 말할게 난 널 사랑해!
When all is said and done
모든 것이 끝나면
I'm home Welcome back, it's hot pot tonight
나 왔어! 어서 와, 오늘 밤은 스키야키다!
Come, gather everyone Let's enjoy this meal
모두 어서 모여! 이 요리를 즐기자!
For another crazy tomorrow
내일은 또 정신없을 거야
What next? What next? In the end, wake up
뭔데? 또 뭐지? 결국 깨어나!
Nobody is out here because of the fog.
안개 때문에 아무도 안 나왔네
-What the hell was that? -Jashin-chan, help!
- 대체 뭐였지? - 사신짱, 도와줘!
Medusa, what's going--?
메두사, 뭐 하는...?
Zombies?
좀비?
Over here! Medusa, hurry up! Run!
이리 와, 메두사! 서둘러, 뛰라고!
Wait!
잠깐
It's locked!
잠겼어
Damn it, who would lock it?
제기랄, 누가 잠근 거야?
Jashin-chan, look!
사신짱, 저기!
Nice find, Medusa.
잘 찾았어, 메두사
-Jashin-chan. -What is it?
- 사신짱 - 왜?
Here's some light.
여기 손전등이 있다
Hey, it's too bright.
얘, 너무 밝잖아
I'll turn it off so they won't catch us.
끌게, 그래야 좀비가 우리를 못 잡을 거야
-Let's hide in here. -Okay.
- 이 안에 숨자 - 그래
Come out. Orochimaru.
나와라, 오로치마루
Orochimaru...
오로치마루...
You guys okay in there?
너희 괜찮니?
Minos, you saved us!
미노스, 네가 우릴 구했어
It's not safe here. They're gathered in the back.
여긴 위험해 그들이 뒤편에 모여 있어
-Should we go outside, then? -That's risky, too.
- 그럼 나가는 게 나을까? - 그것도 위험해
The fog's too thick to see anything.
안개가 너무 심해서 아무것도 안 보여
Then where should we go?
그러면 우리는 어디로 가야 해?
Come with me.
날 따라와
Run for your life!
살고 싶으면 달려!
-We're doomed! -Over here!
- 우리는 죽었다! - 여기야
It's a dead end!
막다른 길이야!
This door is locked, too!
이 문도 잠겼어
Please! Someone, open the door!
누구 없어요? 문을 열어줘요
Please!
제발요!
-It's a sliding door. -Yurine!
- 이건 미닫이문이다 - 유리네!
Oh, whoops.
아, 이런
-Hurry, Medusa! -Help!
- 빨리, 메두사 - 살려줘
Hey, don't abandon me! Help!
날 버리지 마! 살려줘!
Medusa! Minos! Save me, please!
메두사! 미노스! 제발 날 구해줘!
Someone please!
누가 좀!
Jashin-chan.
사신짱
Are you okay? You were having a nightmare.
괜찮니? 넌 악몽을 꿨어
I'm fine.
난 괜찮아
Please don't scream in middle of the night.
한밤에 비명 지르지 마
Okay, I won't.
그래, 안 그럴게
KONNYAKU
'곤약'
If you place a damp towel on someone's feet while they're asleep,
잠자는 사람의 발에 젖은 수건을 얹으면
they're more prone to nightmares!
악몽을 꾸기 쉽죠
The evil preys on the good-hearted.
악마는 착한 사람을 이용하려고 한다
An angel of sorrow rises up against them.
슬픈 천사가 그들을 막으려고 일어선다
What does the angel want to protect?
그 천사는 무엇을 보호하려는 걸까?
Dropkick on My Devil!
사신짱 드롭킥!
Next time, a single-winged angel will steal your heart!
다음 화에서 한쪽 날개의 천사가 여러분 마음을 뺏습니다!